さて　首尾は上々と
Everything went splendidly.
随分とつまらない瑣事に俺を煩わせたものだな
That was quite the pathetic trifle you've troubled me with, Tokiomi.
時臣
恐縮であります　王の中の王
I am very grateful, king of all kings...
King of Heroes, Gilgamesh.
「英雄王」ギルガメッシュよ
Your actions tonight will establish
your prowess as the King of Heroes.
今宵の仕儀は　英雄王の威光を知らしめ
さらに狩り落とすべき獅子がどれなのかを見定めるべく
They will also reveal which of our foes we must hunt down.
今後に備えた露払いでございます
どうか　今しばらくお待ちを
Please stay your hand a little longer.
良かろう
Very well.
For the time being, I shall amuse myself with some exploring.
まだ当面は散策だけで無聊を慰められそうだ
This age is rather fascinating to me.
この時代　なかなかどうして面白い
Is the modern world to your liking?
お気に召されましたか　現代の世界は
度し難いほどに醜悪だ
It's unspeakably ugly.
But there are ways I can enjoy it.
が　それはそれで愛でようもある
肝心なのは
What's important is whether there are any treasures here that are worth adding to my collection.
ここにオレの財に加えるに値するだけの宝物があるかどうかだ
If nothing in this world is worthy of my adoration,
もし　我が寵愛に値するものが何一つない世界であったなら
you will pay dearly for summoning me and wasting my time, Tokiomi.
無益な召喚で俺に無駄足を踏ませた罪は重いぞ　時臣
Worry not.
ご安心を
The Holy Grail will surely please you, King of Heroes.
聖杯は必ずや英雄王のお気に召すことでしょう
That is something for me to determine.
それは俺が検めて決めること
Well, I'll play along with your cajolery for now.
まあいい　当面はお前の口車に乗ってやろう
Everything of value in this world belongs to me.
この世の総ての財宝は俺の物
その聖杯がどの程度の宝であれ
No matter how precious a treasure this Grail of yours may be,
I won't let those mongrels fight over it without my permission.
俺の許しもなしに雑種が奪い合うなど
見過ごせる話ではないからな
時臣　委細は任せておくぞ
I'll leave the details to you, Tokiomi.
My, my.
Honestly.
まったく　よりによってギルガメッシュが
Gilgamesh just had to materialize under the Archer class, which comes with the skill Independent Action.
「単独行動」スキル保有のアーチャークラスに現界するとは
Well, I can just let Kirei take things from here.
まあ　当面のところは綺礼に任せておけばいい
今のところは予定通りだ
For now, everything is proceeding as planned.
Utw
Presents
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
繰り返す世界 何度手を伸ばしたら
How many times must I reach my hand out to this repeating world
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
繰り返す世界 何度手を伸ばしたら
How many times must I reach my hand out to this repeating world
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasu no
儚い涙は黒い心溶かすの？
For the fleeting tears to soften my black heart?
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasu no
儚い涙は黒い心溶かすの？
For the fleeting tears to soften my black heart?
Mebaedashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
芽生え出した思いが胸に響いたなら
If these awakened feelings resonated in my heart
Mebaedashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
芽生え出した思いが胸に響いたなら
If these awakened feelings resonated in my heart
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
君の隣でずっと変わらず護るだろう
I'd stand guard beside you forever and ever
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
君の隣でずっと変わらず護るだろう
I'd stand guard beside you forever and ever
Ochita kibou wo hirotte
堕ちた希望を拾って
If I could pick up these fallen hopes
Ochita kibou wo hirotte
堕ちた希望を拾って
If I could pick up these fallen hopes
Asu ni tsunaide yukeba
明日に繋いでゆけば
And link them on to tomorrow
Asu ni tsunaide yukeba
明日に繋いでゆけば
And link them on to tomorrow
Karamatta ibitsu na negai datte hodokeru
絡まった歪な願いだってほどける
Even these entwined, twisted wishes will come apart
Karamatta ibitsu na negai datte hodokeru
絡まった歪な願いだってほどける
Even these entwined, twisted wishes will come apart
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
光をかざして躊躇いを消した
I've held up the light and erased my hesitation
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
光をかざして躊躇いを消した
I've held up the light and erased my hesitation
Agetakatta no wa mirai de
あげたかったのは未来で
What I wanted to give you is in the future
Agetakatta no wa mirai de
あげたかったのは未来で
What I wanted to give you is in the future
Naiteru yoru daita mama
泣いてる夜抱いたまま
Crying and embracing the night
Naiteru yoru daita mama
泣いてる夜抱いたまま
Crying and embracing the night
Nageki wo sakende
嘆きを叫んで
Screaming its grief out loud
Nageki wo sakende
嘆きを叫んで
Screaming its grief out loud
Fumiireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga
踏み入れた足を遠くの理想が
The distant ideals gently heal
Fumiireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga
踏み入れた足を遠くの理想が
The distant ideals gently heal
Sotto iyashite yuku
そっと癒してゆく
These legs that've stepped forward
Sotto iyashite yuku
そっと癒してゆく
These legs that've stepped forward
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigirisusumou
確かな絆を強く握り進もう
I'll hold on tight to these definite bonds as I advance
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigirisusumou
確かな絆を強く握り進もう
I'll hold on tight to these definite bonds as I advance
Dokomade mo
どこまでも
No matter where I go
Dokomade mo
どこまでも
No matter where I go
Kegarekitta kiseki wo se ni
穢れきった奇跡を背に
I'll shoulder these tainted miracles
Kegarekitta kiseki wo se ni
穢れきった奇跡を背に
I'll shoulder these tainted miracles
アサシンがやられた
Assassin got killed?!
おい　ライダー　進展だぞ
Hey, Rider! This is a big deal!
One of the seven's already been eliminated.
さっそく一人脱落だ
おい
Hey.
The Imperial
Army
おい　わかってるのかよ　アサシンがやられたんだよ
Hey! Don't you get it?!
Assassin got killed!
あい　もう聖杯戦争始まってるんだ
The Holy Grail War has begun!
僕はこうして偵察しているのに
I've been working so hard to gather information,
yet day after day after day,
お前は毎日　毎日　毎日　毎日
煎餅齧ってビデオ見てるだけじゃないか
you just sit around eating rice crackers and watching videos!
You're worse than a familiar! Worse than a rat!
使い魔以下だぞ　ネズミ以下だ
Also, didn't I tell you to take spirit form when I don't need you?
だいたい　必要ない時は霊体化してろて言ってるだろう
そのための魔力だって僕が供給してるんだぞ
I have to supply you with more mana otherwise, you know!
あのなー　暗殺者如きが何だというのだ
Look, nobody cares about Assassin.
He's only good at skulking in the shadows.
隠れ潜むのだけが取り柄のアサシンなんぞ
余の敵ではあるまいに
He could never pose a threat to me.
それよりも　坊主
More importantly, boy...
This is far more amazing!
凄いのはこれだ　これ
This big black thing they call a B-2.
ほれ　このB2という黒くてデカイやつ
素晴らしい
It's magnificent!
I'm thinking of buying around ten of them. What do you think?
こいつを十機ばかり購入したいのだが　どうか
It'd probably be less trouble to just buy
countries outright, considering the cost.
その金で国を買い取った方が早いぞ　きっと
おー　そうかー　やはり問題は資金の調達か
I see.
So, the problem is where to get all that money.
Were there some affluent capital nearby, such as Persepolis, we could simply go forth and raid it.
どっかにペルセポリスぐらい富んだ都があるなら
手っ取り早く略奪するんだがのう
For the moment, this Clinton man will be our biggest obstacle.
取り敢えず　このクリントンとかいう男が当面の難敵だな
He will prove to be a more formidable opponent than Darius III.
ダレイオス王以来の手強い敵になりそうだ
A-At any rate, I'm glad that Assassin was eliminated first.
まあ　何にせよ
真っ先に脱落したのがアサシンだったのは有り難い
お前はどうせ真正面から敵にぶつかっていくタイプだろう
You're the type to always take the enemy head-on, right?
So it's best for us that the guy who'd use sneak attacks and tricks is out.
変に奇策で足下掬おうとしてくるような奴がいなくなったのは好都合だ
このトマホークとか言うのも使えそうだ
This Tomahawk thing looks to be useful, too!
セイバー　ランサー　アーチャーの三大騎士クラス
Saber, Lancer, Archer, the three great knight classes,
そして暴れるだけが能のバーサーカーは
and Berserker, who only knows how to thrash around.
お前のあの宝具をもってすれば　まったく畏れるに足りない
They're all small fry in the face of that Noble Phantasm of yours!
Which just leaves Caster as a potential threat.
後　厄介そうなのはキャスターだ
あいつの正体さえ掴めれば　もう
If we can find out who Caster is, we'll-
アサシンはどうやられた
How did Assassin fall?
Fool. I'm asking about the Servant that defeated Assassin.
だから　アサシンを倒したサーヴァントだ
You saw him, didn't you?
見ていたのであろう
I think he was Tohsaka's Servant.
たぶん　遠坂のサーヴァントだと思う
His appearance, his attacks, everything about him was gold and flashy.
姿格好といい　攻撃といい
やたら金ピカで派手な奴だった
It all happened so fast, I couldn't tell...
ともかく一瞬のことで　何が何やら
たわけ
Fool!
余が戦うとすれば　それは勝ち残って生きている方であろうが
If I must fight someone, it will be to survive and win!
そっちを仔細に観察せんでどうする
Why weren't you paying close attention to him?
Well, it matters not.
まあ　何でもいいわ
その金ビカだか何だかを見て
Did you observe anything else of note about the flashy gold guy?
ほかに気になるようなことはなかったか
B-But it all happened in the middle of the night...
そ　そんなこと言ったって　夜中だし
It was over in an instant...
本当一瞬の
Hey, Rider, a Servant normally only has one Noble Phantasm, right?
なあ　ライダー
サーヴァントの宝具って　普通は一つ限りだよな
原則としてはな
As a rule, yes.
まあ　宝具を数で捉えようとするのは意味がない
However, "how many" isn't the right way to conceptualize Noble Phantasms.
知っておろうが　宝具というのは
As you may know, Noble Phantasms are the
physical manifestation of a Hero's legend or tale.
その英霊に纏わるとりわけ有名な故事や逸話が具現化したものであって
ひとつの特殊能力　一種類の攻撃手段といった場合もある
It can be a specific ability or method of attack.
Is there some Noble Phantasm that consists of throwing dozens of swords at an opponent?
じゃあ　剣を十本も二十本も投げつける「宝具」ってのもありか
A sword that splits into many copies, huh?
無数に分裂する剣か
有り得るな　それは単一の「宝具」として定義しうる能力だ
It's possible.
That could still qualify as a single Noble Phantasm.
But those weren't copies.
Each weapon had a different shape.
でも　あれは分裂したというのは
あまりに一つ一つの形が違いすぎる
まあ　いいわ
Well, forget it.
We'll learn the enemy's identity when we encounter him.
敵の正体なんぞは　いずれ相見えたときに知れることだ
A-Are you sure that's okay?
そ　そんなんでいいのかよ
I am!
良い　むしろ心が躍る
In fact, it's more fun this way!
Food, sex, sleep, and war.
食事にセックス　眠りに戦
何事につけても存分に愉しみ抜く
Whatever you do, enjoy it to the fullest.
That is the secret of life.
それが人生の秘訣であろう
さあ　ではそろそろ外に楽しみを求めてみようか
Now, let us go find some entertainment outside.
We're heading out, boy! Get ready!
出陣だ　坊主　支度せい
H-Heading out? Where?
しゅ　出陣って　どこへ
Somewhere, anywhere.
どこか適当に　そこら辺へ
Oh, come on!
ふざけるなよ
遠坂を見張っていたのは貴様だけではあるまい
You weren't the only one watching Tohsaka's place.
This means everyone else also knows of Assassin's death.
となれば　アサシンの死も知れ渡っていよう
ここからはほかの連中が一斉に動き出すぞ
All the other teams will be making their move tonight.
そやつらを見つけた端から狩ってゆく
We'll crush them as we come across them.
Crush them as we come across them, you say...
見つけて狩るって
そんな簡単に
That won't be easy.
I am Rider.
余はライダー
こと脚に関しては他のサーヴァントより優位におるぞ
My mobility far exceeds that of any other Servant.
Wait, wait, wait! Not here! You'll blow the house away!
待て待て待て　ここじゃまずい　家が吹っ飛ぶ
サーヴァント消失
I have lost my Servant.
マスターの権利失効によるし
I have forfeited my right as Master and can no longer participate in the Holy Grail War.
聖杯戦争は継続不能
約定に従い　言峰綺礼は聖堂教会による身柄の保護を要求します
In accordance to the treaty, I, Kotomine Kirei, ask that the Church shelter and protect me.
I accept your request.
受諾する
In my role as judge, I, Kotomine Risei, will guarantee your safety.
監督役の責務に則って
言峰璃正があなたの身の安全を保証する
Now, come in.
さあ　奥へ
父上　誰かこの教会を見張っている者は
Father, is anyone watching this church?
ない
No. This place has been declared a neutral sanctuary.
ここは中立地帯として不可侵が保証されている
余計な干渉をしたマスターは教会からの諫言がある
The Holy Church will censure any Master who defies the decree.
では　安泰ということですね
It's safe here, then.
Yes.
念のため　警戒は怠るな
Don't let your guard down, just in case.
Post one of you to keep watch here at all times.
常に一人はここに配置するように
Yes. Understood.
はっ　かしこまりました
現場の監視をしていた者は
Who was watching the battle?
私が確認したところ
I detected the presence of familiars from four separate Masters.
異なる気配の使い魔は四種類
一昨日　最後のサーヴァント「キャスター」の現界を確認した
Two days ago, the summoning of the final Servant, Caster, was confirmed.
All of the Grail War Servants should now be present, but...
此度の聖杯戦争のサーヴァントはすべて出揃っているはずだが
There's one missing.
一人足りないか
できれば　全てのマスターに見せておきたかったところだが
I was hoping all the Masters would see it.
今の局面で御三家の邸宅を監視することは
At this point, surveilling the estates of the Three Families is a Master's obvious course of action.
マスターとして当然の策でございましょう
If he couldn't even think to do that, it wouldn't
occur to him to guard against us Assassins anyway.
その程度の用心も怠るような者であれば
どのみち俺らアサシンを警戒する神経など持ち合わせておりますまい
The Masters have their backs open, believing Assassin to be dead.
アサシンが排除されたものと油断しきっているマスターたちの背後に
We, already Heroic Spirits of the shadows, shall become true shadow.
我ら影の英霊は
今度こそ本物の影になる
The battle has begun.
これで　戦端は開かれた
いよいよ始まるぞ　第四次聖杯戦争が
At last, it is time for the 4th Holy Grail War to start.
These old eyes of mine will finally see a miracle incarnate.
この老骨も　今度こそ奇跡の成就を見届けられそうだ
ここが 切嗣の生まれた国
So this is where Kiritsugu was born.
How did you enjoy your journey in the sky, Saber?
どう セイバー  空の旅の感想は
別段 どうということも
It was nothing much to speak of.
Far less exciting than I had anticipated.
期待していたよりは味気ないものでした
I suppose flying is nothing to a Heroic Spirit like you.
英霊ともなれば 空を飛ぶくらい驚くほどでもないかしら
That's not it.
そういうわけでは
サーヴァントは現界する際に 現代の知識を与えられますから
Servants receive knowledge of the
modern world upon materialization.
いざとなれば  この飛行機という機械を乗りこなすことも可能です
I could even pilot this aircraft if it came to it.
You could pilot it?
操縦 できるの
My Riding skill allows me to command any beast or vehicle, with the exception of divine and mythical beasts.
私の「騎乗」スキルは 幻獣 神獣を除いて
乗り物という概念すべてに適用される能力ですから
鞍に跨り手綱を握れば あとは直感で何とかなります
Once I mount the saddle and take the reins, intuition does the rest.
Mount the saddle and take the reins...
鞍に跨り手綱を
Did I say something funny?
私は笑われるようなことを言いましたか
No.
Still, you must be the only Servant who
has flown in an airplane in physical form.
あなただけよね
I apologize for that.
その点は申し訳ありません　私が霊体化できないばかりに
If only I could take spirit form...
No, I didn't mean it like that.
Don't worry about it.
そういう意味じゃないのよ　気にしないで
あなた　いくら見てても飽きないし
I never get tired of watching you.
Irisviel, is there something strange about me?
アイリスフィール　何か変わった事でも
ううん　何でもないのよ
No, not at all.
貴女がそういう笑い方をするときは
When you laugh like that, it means
there's some hidden meaning behind it.
何か含むところがあってのこと
What is it? I want you to be frank with me.
何でしょう　正直に言ってほしい
It means that your being stuck in
physical form isn't without its merits.
あなたがずっと実体なのは　何も悪いことばかりじゃないってこと
It's given me many enjoyable hours choosing outfits for you.
おかげで私には　あなたの服を選ぶ楽しみが増えたもの
Irisviel, is this manner of dress actually common in this era?
アイリスフィール　本当に私のこの格好は
この時代に馴染むものなのですか
I chose it to match my own outfit.
私との釣り合いを取って選んだ服なんだけれど　気に入らない
You don't like it?
いえ別に　それなりに動きやすくありますし　男装には慣れていますから
No, it's fine.
It is rather easy to move in, and besides, I'm used to dressing as a man.
凄い活気ねえ
What a lively place!
Kiritsugu should have already arrived, yes?
すでに切嗣も この地に辿り着いてる手筈でしたね
Yes. Twelve hours before us.
ええ  半日早くね
He'll come find us, so don't worry.
でも 向こうから見つけてくれるから  大丈夫よ
We'll keep an eye on the situation for now, so we can act when the time comes.
当面は状況の変化を見極めながら 柔軟に臨機応変に
It's rare that I get to visit Japan, so I'd
like to enjoy it before the fighting starts.
せっかくの日本だもの
戦いが始まる前に 満喫しておかないと
That's dangerous.
危険です
We should secure our base of operations,
meet up with Kiritsugu, and discuss our plans.
どこかに拠点を構えてから
切嗣を交えて いったん方策を詰めるべきです
I suppose you're right...
それはそうだとは思うけれど  もったいないじゃない
But wouldn't it be a waste?
We've come all this way.
せっかくこんな遠い国に来たんだし
And...
それに
It's my first time.
私ね  初めてなの
だから  外の世界を出歩くのは
It's the first time I've ventured into the outside world.
これが 初めてなの
You spent your entire life in that castle?
では貴女は  これまでの生涯を
ずっとあの城で
私は 聖杯戦争のために造られた人形だったから
I am a mere puppet created for the Holy Grail War.
Of course, it's not like I don't know anything about it.
もちろん 何も知らないわけじゃないのよ
Kiritsugu told me all about the outside world using videos and pictures.
切嗣が映画とか  写真とか
外の世界の景色や出来事をいっぱい教えてくれたもの
This is the first time I've seen it with my own eyes, though.
でも この目で本当に世界を見るのは これが初めて
だから
So...
御免なさい はしゃぎ過ぎちゃった
Forgive me. I got carried away.
止めてください
Please stop the car.
Walking in this city will also be a new experience for me.
私とて この街を歩くのは初めての経験ですが
エスコートは騎士の役目
It is a knight's duty to escort.
I shall do my very best.
及ばずながら努力します
さあ  どうか
Come with me.
The equipment you requested has arrived.
装備品一式全て到着しております
Madam and Saber have arrived as well and are making their way together.
マダム達もすでに冬木に到着し 動き始めています
That way, the other Masters will assume Madam is Saber's Master.
これでほかのマスターたちは マダムをセイバーのマスターと思い込む事と
Good.
わかった
昨夜 遠坂邸で動きがありました
There was an incident last night at the Tohsaka mansion.
Here is the recorded footage.
記録した影像です
この展開 どう見る
What do you make of this?
出来過ぎのように思えます
It looks too good to be true.
アサシンの侵入から
The time span between Assassin's trespassing
and the Tohsaka Servant's response is too short.
遠坂のサーヴァントの攻撃までのタイムラグが短すぎます
気配遮断スキルを持つアサシンを
Since Assassin has a skill that masks his presence,
it's hard to believe he was detected in advance.
事前に察知できたとは思えませんし
I think Tohsaka was expecting an intruder.
侵入者があることを承知していたのではないかと
サーヴァント戦では  英霊の正体を秘匿するのが鉄則だ
In a battle among Servants, it's critical to conceal the identities of Heroic Spirits.
Why would Tohsaka expose his Servant for all to see?
何故遠坂はみすみすサーヴァントを晒すような真似をした
He had a reason to, I suppose.
見せる意図があったということでしょうか
うん 舞弥
Maiya, what became of Assassin's Master?
アサシンのマスターはどうなった
He escaped to the church last night.
昨夜のうちに教会に避難し
The judge decreed him under his protection.
監督役が保護下に置いた旨告知されました
Assassin's Master is Kotomine Kirei.
アサシンのマスターは言峰綺礼
Maiya, send a familiar to watch the Fuyuki city church.
舞弥
冬木教会に使い魔を放っておけ
Are you sure?
いいのですか
Masters are forbidden from operating in
the neutral zone surrounding the church.
教会の不可侵地帯にマスターが干渉するのは禁じられているはずですが
Keep it as close as you can without the priest noticing.
監督役の神父にバレないよう
ギリギリの距離をうろつかせておけばいい
Very well. Understood.
はい わかりました
Where is the thing I left with you?
預けておいたやつは どこだ
Here.
こちらに
About two seconds.
二秒ってところか
I'm surprised.
衰えたな
Yes.
はい
Ilya weighs less than that Walther.
そこのワルサーよりも
イリヤの体重は軽いんだ
Yet...
もう　八歳になるのに
She's already eight years old.
Focus only on what matters now.
いま必要なことだけに意識を向けてください
余計なことは 考えないで
Don't think about anything else.
素敵 まるで夜空の合わせ鏡みたい
It's so beautiful.
Just like a mirror reflecting the night sky.
It's so much fun to walk around a new town, accompanied by a gentleman.
殿方に付き添われて見知らぬ町を歩くのは
とても楽しいわね
Did I make an acceptable gentleman?
殿方の紛い物で  事足りましたか
You were perfect.
非の打ち所もなかったわ
You were a wonderful knight today.
今日のあなたはとっても素敵なナイトだったわよ
光栄です
You honor me, my princess.
姫
Saber, do you like the sea?
セイバー 海は好き
I suppose I don't really know.
好きと言われると  どうだか
In my age and country, the sea was where my enemies arrived.
私の時代の  私の国では
海の彼方は つねに夷狄の押し寄せてくる場所でしたから
I've hated it, but never once have I admired it.
忌々しく思うことはあっても
憧れたことはありません
何だか 申し訳ないわ
I'm sorry about that.
You're a woman just like me.
あなただって同じ女なのに
Yet, when you were King Arthur, you
couldn't afford to enjoy anything like this.
アーサー王として生きてきたあなたには
こんな風に楽しむ余裕なんてなかったのよね
And you, Irisviel?
アイリスフィールこそ
Would you not have preferred walking
around the city with Kiritsugu instead?
本当は私ではなく
切嗣と街を歩きたかったのではないですか
I couldn't make him do that.
あの人は  駄目よ
It would only hurt his feelings.
辛い想いをさせてしまうわ
切嗣は貴女と過ごす時間を楽しまないのですか
Does Kiritsugu not enjoy spending time with you?
He's someone who finds happiness painful.
あの人は幸福であることに苦痛を感じてしまう人だから
敵のサーヴァント
An enemy Servant.
Yes.
はい
He's making his presence known from the shadows, 100 meters from here.
100メートルほど先の物陰から
気配を漂わせています
He seems to be inviting us there.
どうやら  我々を誘っているようですね
How thoughtful.
律儀ね
So he wishes to choose the battlefield.
戦う場所を選ぼうってわけ
Shall we take him up on his offer?
お招きに与るとする
We shall.
望むところです
Rider, let's go back down.
ライダー  早く 降りよう  ここ
Right now!
早く
What? This is the perfect vantage point.
何を言う 見張るには誂え向きの場所ではないか
I-I'm gonna fall!
降りる いや  降ろせ
I mean, take me down!
も も    もう嫌
I-I can't take this anymore...
落ち着きのない奴め
Don't be so impatient.
Waiting is also an important part of war!
坐して待つのも戦のうちだぞ
I wanna go home.
帰りたい  イギリスに帰りたい
I wanna go home to England...
I already told you to stop being so impatient.
そう急くなと言っておろうに
Look. It appears that things have begun to unfold.
ほれ  状況もようやく動き出しそうだぞ
This will be fun!
盛り上がってきたはいい
よくぞ来た
Welcome.
今日一日 この街を練り歩いて過ごしたものの
I have spent the entire day searching this city.
Yet, everyone simply hides away in their little holes.
どいつもこいつも穴熊を決め込むばかり
俺の誘いに応じた猛者は  お前だけだ
You, brave one, are the only one who responded to my invitation.
That pristine valor...
その清澄な闘気
You are Saber, I presume?
セイバーとお見受けしたが  如何に
Indeed.
いかにも そういうお前はランサーに相違ないな
And you must be Lancer.
これより死合おうという相手と
I regret we cannot exchange names even
though we shall be fighting to the death.
尋常に名乗りを交わすこともままならぬとは
It is the fault of those unfortunate rules.
興の乗らぬ縛りがあったものだ
Saber, be careful.
セイバー 気をつけて
私でも治癒魔術ぐらいのサポートは出来るけど
I can use healing magic to support you,
but nothing more.
でも それ以上は
Leave Lancer to me.
ランサーはお任せを
It worries me more that the other Master is nowhere to be seen.
ただ  相手のマスターガ姿を見せないのが気がかりです
They may be plotting something.
妙な策を弄するかもしれない
Please be careful.
注意しておいてください
アイリスフィール
Irisviel, please cover my back.
私の背中は貴女にお任せします
Very well, Saber.
わかったわ セイバー
Bring me victory!
この私に勝利を
Yes, without fail.
はい 必ずや
Episode 3
Land of Winter Trees
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Omoide ni yorisoinagara
If I can find peace in my recollections
思い出に寄り添いながら
Omoide ni yorisoinagara
If I can find peace in my recollections
思い出に寄り添いながら
Kimi wo omoeru nara
While reminiscing about you
君を想えるなら
Kimi wo omoeru nara
While reminiscing about you
君を想えるなら
Itsumo minareteru madobe ni utsutta
I am all too familiar with the window reflection
いつも見慣れてる窓辺に映った
Itsumo minareteru madobe ni utsutta
I am all too familiar with the window reflection
いつも見慣れてる窓辺に映った
Sono hitomi wa ashita wo muite ita
Of your eyes that were gazing into the future
その瞳は明日を向いていた
Sono hitomi wa ashita wo muite ita
Of your eyes that were gazing into the future
その瞳は明日を向いていた
Ah sakaraenu sadame to shitte mo
Ah, even though I know there's no escaping this fate
あぁ 逆らえぬ運命と知っても
Ah sakaraenu sadame to shitte mo
Ah, even though I know there's no escaping this fate
あぁ 逆らえぬ運命と知っても
Kowakunai kokoro kara shinjite iru
I'm not afraid. I have faith from the bottom of my heart
怖くない 心から信じている
Kowakunai kokoro kara shinjite iru
I'm not afraid. I have faith from the bottom of my heart
怖くない 心から信じている
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Shizuka ni utsuriyuku
Amidst the quietly shifting
静かに移りゆく
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Tooi kioku no naka
Distant memories
遠い記憶の中
Kimi to sugoshita akashi wa
Proof of the time I spent with you
君と過ごした証は
Kimi to sugoshita akashi wa
Proof of the time I spent with you
君と過ごした証は
Tashika ni koko ni aru
Is right here with me
確かにここにある
Tashika ni koko ni aru
Is right here with me
確かにここにある
Afuredasu kimochi wo
You've shown me what it means
溢れ出す気持ちを
Afuredasu kimochi wo
You've shown me what it means
溢れ出す気持ちを
Oshiete kureta kara
To have overflowing feelings
教えてくれたから
Oshiete kureta kara
To have overflowing feelings
教えてくれたから
Kono sekai ga nakunatte mo
Even if this world were to end
この世界がなくなっても
Kono sekai ga nakunatte mo
Even if this world were to end
この世界がなくなっても
Watashi wa soko ni iru
I'll be right by your side
私はそこにいる
Watashi wa soko ni iru
I'll be right by your side
私はそこにいる
Let's see what you can do, adorable King of Knights.
では お手並み拝見だ
かわいい騎士王さん
セイバークラスの抗魔力は伊達ではないか
The anti-magic skill of a Saber-class Servant is no fairy tale.
この男  できる
He's good.
戯れ合いはそこまでだ  ランサー
That's enough fun, Lancer.
何が起こっているの
What's happening?
行きます  連れて行け馬鹿
I'll go! Take me, you idiot!
Next Episode
Blade of the Demonic Spear